http://www.icspublications.org/pages/privacy-policy

Save 40% when you buy $100 of ICS titles with code ICSBULK. Discount terms and conditions apply.
My Account
Welcome to ICS Publications!
Teresa of Avila
Thérèse of Lisieux (the Little Flower)
My Account
Welcome to ICS Publications!
Privacy Policy
ICS Publications provides a secure shopping experience, dedicated to protecting your privacy while providing excellent customer service and products. The following Privacy Policy governs the online information collection practices of ICS Publications. Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you while you are using the ICS Publications website and the ways in which we use this information. This Privacy Policy does not necessarily apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of our Site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. Because the Web is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we’ll post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this website and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the Site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified.
How We Collect and Use Information ICS Publications will use voluntarily provided data to:       • obtain customer/marketing feedback       • gather customer information needed to improve service       • communicate offers on merchandise and services which we believe will be of interest to you       • provide you with requested information       • contact you with special promotions or new products       • expand and enhance ICS Publications service, products, and website       • Send you catalogs and direct mail promotions at your request
We do not collect or save your personal info unless you provide it for ordering, or other requests. You may, at any time, request not to receive e-mail promotions, and/or to be taken off a previously requested mailing list. We may collect and store personal or other information that you voluntarily supply to us online while using the Site (e.g., while on the Site or in responding via email to a feature provided on the Site).
Cookies  We may collect information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, which allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic on the Site. We also may use a standard feature found in browser software called a "cookie" to enhance your experience with the Site. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies store bits of information in a secure area. This information is readable only by ICS Publications, and helps us provide you with individualized service. Cookies cannot deliver a virus, and we DO NOT share saved cookie data.
By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us deliver advertisements, identify how many unique users visit us, and track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the Site where you may have entered preference information before.
Disabling Cookies  Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookie files on your computer by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying you when such as file is stored. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you do elect to disable the ICS Publications cookie you may not be able to take full advantage of a personalized experience at ICS Publications or any of its websites.
We may also ask you to voluntarily provide information in a few circumstances. When you purchase items from ICS Publications, we will ask you to voluntarily provide certain personally identifiable information, such as, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card number. We need this information to process and fulfill your order and notify you of order status. Other examples of when we may ask you to voluntarily provide personally identifiable information include if you subscribe to our email program (information such as your name and email address), choose to provide us preference information (such as interests, product preferences, and items purchased), or when you enter one of our promotions (information such as name, address and telephone number).
Any personal information that you may share with us is kept absolutely private. We do make our mailing list information available to carefully screened companies whose products or services might interest you. If you prefer to have your name withheld, simply contact us and let us know. If you order by mail or phone and do not want to have your name traded with nonaffiliated companies, please call 1-800-832-8489. You can also contact us via e-mail at business@icspublications.org. Please include your name and mailing address in the message.
Promotional emails  ICS Publications may send you e-mails with promotional offers or information related to ICS Publications products or services only if you opt-in to receiving such e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive e-mailed special event information, sales notifications or other messages from ICS Publications, please click here and follow the “unsubscribe” instructions. Your e-mail address will be removed from our marketing list.
Accessing my ICS Publications online information  You can personalize your experience at www.icspublications.org by becoming a registered user. Once registered, you can review and maintain your account information at any time. Your account information is secure and is accessible by using a password that you select. To become a registered user at www.icspublications.org, or to modify your current preferences, click here.
Safety of your Financial Information  We use Secure Socket Layers (SSL), the industry standard in transferring information to process your orders. The SSL encrypts, or translates, your order information into a highly indecipherable code, which is processed immediately.
Your Transactions are Secure When you've finished shopping and begin the checkout process, you will move into the secure area of our site. A warning window may pop up to notify you that you are entering this "safe" area. Once you've entered, the page address (URL) will change from http to https, to let you know you are in a secure area. Also, a key or a closed lock will appear in your browser screen to notify you of this change. You will remain in this secure zone for the entire checkout process.
Notification of changes to the Privacy Policy  This policy is subject to change and the changes will become effective immediately. If there are material changes to this policy, we will provide notice of the changes by posted the amended policy on www.icspublications.org and by revising the effective date of the Privacy Policy textual link appearing at the bottom of the page.
Effective September 2016
International Shipping
Frequently Asked Questions
Returns
Call Us - Mon-Fri 9:00-5:00 EST
ICS Publications
About Us
ICS: The Institute
Thérèse of Lisieux (the Little Flower)
Join our email list and save immediately. You'll also be the first to know about coupons and special promotions.
Click Here to Subscribe
© 2020 ICS Publications | Shopify Theme by Mile High Themes | Privacy Policy | Terms and Conditions
Powered by Shopify
x
